ojas-gujarat.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - OJAS Gujarat

www.ojas-gujarat.in Website created as a resource to help people know about latest recruitment, exams and results, answer key, admit cad etc. The site primarily focused on Government jobs, bank jobs, railway jobs, defence jobs, private jobs, exam results, exam admit card, and more. It intends to be a great platform for job seekers without getting involved in legal suits. So, here is the disclaimer policy for www.ojas-gujarat.in

The content provided by www.ojas-gujarat.in is solely for informational purposes only and we hold no right whatsoever for all the activity that a visitor (you) does on other web pages linked from www.ojas-gujarat.in  
Since we verify every information at the time of publishing them on ojas-gujarat.in and we (ojas-gujarat.in) can’t be held any response for any type of changes made to original rules, notifications by an organization, institution, bank and department at a later date. It’s your task to ensure and take care of official notifications, announcement by visiting official website.

**Privacy Policy:**  
The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ojas-gujarat.in and how it is used.

Log Files  
Like many other Web sites, ojas-gujarat.in makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
Double Click DART Cookie  
Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on www.ojas-gujarat.in  
· Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.ojas-gujarat.in. and other sites on the Internet.  
· Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Google Adsense These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ojas-gujarat.in send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. ojas-gujarat.in has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. ojas-gujarat.in privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Terms & Conditions

**User Agreement:**  
Visitors are informed to read the Term of Use before going to access any content or data published on our website or in www.ojas-gujarat.in. It is informed to all the visitors who are viewing our site have to accept the Policy conditions. By accessing our site information you are agreeing to the Terms and conditions of our site www.ojas-gujarat.in.  
**Copy right:**  
All the content available in the site including text, written content , graphical images and intellectual property are unregistered and registered by the website owner. Reproducing the information available in the website strictly prohibited. However, the written content can be reproduced in whole or part with the permission of admin.  
**Right to change:**  
Modification can be done in the Terms of Use without any information. Modifications in the policies are available at our website By accessing our site information you are agreeing to the Terms and conditions of our site www.ojas-gujarat.in. If visitor continue to visit our website without viewing modifications in Terms of Use, it refers to accepting our conditions and policies.  
**Acceptance of Privacy Policy:**  
By using our website, you will be treated as accepted for Privacy Statement. If you are not satisfied with our privacy statement you can discontinue using our website.  
**Links to third party websites:**  
On our website we are providing links to websites which are operated by third party vendors. We are not responsible for any modifications done in the attached links. By accessing to the third party websites, it is your own risk and you may be required to accept the terms and conditions of such websites.
